<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Send Greeting</string>
    <string name="title_activity_share">Send Greeting</string>
    <string-array name="diwali_english_message_list">
        <item>Millions of lamps are illuminating to declare the victory of light,\nI wish you happy diwali with endless happiness and prosperity.\nHappy Diwali to You.</item>
        <item>Wish you A happy diwali filled with fun and happiness.</item>
        <item>On this auspicious day of Diwali Joy,\nhappiness and prosperity Come to your life,\nthrough the light from diwali lamps.</item>
        <item>Celebrate the Festival of light Celebrate and enjoy Diwali Celebrate God’s Victory Happy Diwali to you.</item>
        <item>I wish you a joyful year of prosperity Happy Diwali to you and your family.</item>
        <item>When we say Happy Diwali We say happy for the Victory of god over evil.\nSay Happy Diwali to Dears and nears To express you happiness for the victory of God.</item>
        <item>Diwali is the festival to celebrate the victory of God And that will be a great Diwali only if you spread the spirit of Diwali to those unfortunate Who are not able to celebrate Diwali When you share Diwali to them.\nGod will rejoice and bless you.</item>
        <item>Here’s my greetings to spread the love and blessings of Goddess of Wealth and Beauty.\nMay you all have a splendid and magnificent celebration of Diwali!</item>
        <item>Happy Diwali to you and your family.</item>
        <item>May the light of sparkling Diyas bring your life an everlasting hope,\nfulfillment, happiness and prosperity.\nHave a happy and blessed Diwali!</item>
        <item>I’m sending my warmest greetings to you this Deepavali.\nMay you and your family have a blessed and safe diwali celebration. Have fun!</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="diwali_gujarati_message_list">
        <item>આપને મારા તરફથી દિવાળી ની ખુબ ખુબ શુભેચ્છા..</item>
        <item>આપ સહુને દિવાળીની ખૂબ ખૂબ શુભેચ્છાઓ સહ, નવા વર્ષે ઉગતા  સૂર્યનાં, પ્રકાશિત કિરણોથી ભરપુર, મંગલ જીવન હો, એવી પ્રભુ પાસે અભ્યર્થના …!..જયશ્રીકૃષ્ણ.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="diwali_hindi_message_list">
        <item>Diwali Hindi Messages</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="new_year_english_message_list">
        <item>New Year English Messages</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="new_year_gujarati_message_list">
        <item>આપને નુતન વર્ષની ખુબ ખુબ શુભકામના,આપનું આવનાર વર્ષ સ્નેહ ,ઉલ્લાસ અને પ્રફૂલ્લીતા થી પરિપૂર્ણ રહે એવી મારી અભિલાષા , આમતો પ્રત્યેક વર્ષ આપણા પ્રયાસ પર નિર્ભર છે પણ શુભ કામનાઓ આપણામાં ઉત્સાહ ,મનોબળ , અને સકારાત્મક ઉર્જાનું સિંચન કરે છે આપ સર્વ કામો સકારાત્મક દ્રષ્ટિકોણ થી કરો અને પરિણામો પણ સકારાત્મક અને સંતોષકારક બને તેવી અમારી શુભકામના.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="new_year_hindi_message_list">
        <item>New Year Hindi Messages</item>
    </string-array>

    <!--<string name="banner_home_footer">ca-app-pub-3940256099942544/6300978111</string>-->

    <string name="banner_home_footer">ca-app-pub-9184597918832012/9650889580</string>

    <string name="title_activity_greeting">GreetingActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="nav_diwali">Diwali</string>
    <string name="nav_new_year">New Year</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Diwali</item>
        <item>New Year</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
